Shraddha G S O Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Coding, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Application Support, C, Opencv, C++, Java, Machine learning, deep Neural Networks, VS, Python, SQL Server, Java Script, Mongo DB, PyQT



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: SFO Technologies Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: M.Tech [Medical Software]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Coding, Web Development, Software Testing, Application Support, C, Opency, C++, Java, Neural Networks, VS, Python, SQL Server,

Java Script, MongoDB, PyQT

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Skilled professional with 2 years of experience in Software Development, Application Programming, Coding, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Application Support, C, Opencv, C++, Java, Neural Networks, GUI, VS, Python, SQL Server, Java Script, Mongo DB, PyQT

Work Experience

SFO Technologies as Software Engineer

Aug 2020 to Till Date

Undertaking trainings on chat bot building and DevOps related trainings

Samsung R&D Institute India as Student Trainee

May 2019 to Jul 2020

Research Projects carried out during 14 months of internship,

- 1.Depth Estimation of tissue (ROI) for optimizing X-Ray dosage.
- 2. Segmentation of Scrotal Ultrasound Images and estimate Scrotal

Volume using the U-Net generated Segmentation.

- 3. Analysis of Fetal Heart measurements to generate a Nomogram.
- 4. Detection of COVID-19 in Lung X-Ray images using Deep Learning.

Worked on C++, OpenCV, Python, CMake, MATLAB, SITK, TensorFlow,

Deep Learning concepts, Tensorflow and TfLite

Accenture Pvt Ltd as Associate Software Engineer Sep 2017 to Jul 2018

3ep 2017 to 3ul 2010

Automate the excel work in internal projects using Python. Automate internal websites using Selenium

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Medical Electronics) from M S Ramaiah Institute of Technology, Bangalore in 2017

PG: M.Tech (Medical Software) from Manipal Academy Of Higher Education, Manipal in 2020

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Webinar on Risk Management Approach in Medical Devices as per ISO 14971:2019

Deep Learning A-Z: Hands-On Artificial Neural Networks

Built your own bot certificate of participation

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
MATLAB			
C++			
C#			
OPENCV			
JAVA			
Python			
TensorFlow			
SQL			
JAVA SCRIPT			
Mongodb			
PYQT			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Kannada				

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization